

Luis Mario Amor Sánchez

Software Developer

How to reach me:

GitHub:

https://github.com/luismario2393

Cell:

(+57) 316-6990-917

Email:

luismarioamorsanchez@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/luis-mario-amor-sanchez/

Adress:

Cartagena, Colombia, Blas de lezo plan 400 mz 11 lote 11

Personal Profile

I am a passionate Software developer with more than 2 years of experience, specialized in Front end languages for the development of web and mobile applications. My proactive approach and ability to solve problems autonomously allow me to create exceptional and engaging user experiences.

Educational Training

Sofwate developer

Platzi - UDEMY

- Enrolled from June 2020 to the present
- Taking specialization courses in front end languages to broaden the skill set
- Mobile application courses

Environmental engineer

Fundación Universitaria Tecologico Comfenalco

 Attended from January 2011 to November 2015

Career Summary

Software Developer Frontend

LIFTIT

June 2022 to Nov 2023

- Design and create software solutions for the implementation of the new microfrontend
- Check the feasibility of software prototypes.
- Modify the code to fix bugs.

Software Developer Frontend

WACO

May. 2022 to July 2022

 In Waco I work as a freelance frontend developer, in a project developed with react

Software Developer Frontend

MUNCHER

Nov. 2021 to March 2022

- Design and create software solutions for the implementation of the new front end of the company
- Check the feasibility of software prototypes.

Software Developer Freelance

Freelance

Dic. 2020 to Nov 2021

Professional Skills

Coding Languages:

JavaScript, HTML/CSS, Dart, TypeScript, Node Js

Frameworks/Systems:

React, Recoil, Redux, Next Js, Redux toolkit, Redux saga, styleComponent, Flutter

Character References

Senior Software Developer, Clara Email: davidsantiagoquinto@gmail.com

Bryam Varon

Tech lead Tribu Growth, Liftit Email: bryamvaron@gmail.com